geekversity.com.au 2009-04-15

# Geekversity

## Privacy Policy

Geekdom Pty Limited ( **Geekdom** ), as part of Photon Group Limited, is committed to adopting the highest standards to safeguard our customers’ personal information.

Geekdom, like other companies operating in Australia, is bound by the National Privacy Principles as set out in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and the Privacy Amendment (Private Sector) Act 2000.

Throughout this policy, we refer to your ‘personal information’ which means information which identifies you as an individual or from which your identity can be reasonably ascertained. Your mail address is an example of personal information.

Geekdom’s collection, use and disclosure of personal information is set out below.

### What Personal Information does Geekdom collect and why?

Geekdom collects personal information about you in order to provide personalized internet marketing education and information services. The personal information you provide to Geekdom will enhance the products and services that we offer to you. The type of personal information we collect may include your name, address, telephone numbers, information on how you use our products and services (such as the seminars you attend and information on your browsing activity when visiting one of our websites) and personal preferences. This information permits us to develop products and services to suit your needs.

### How may Geekdom use your personal information?

The personal information you provide Geekdom may be used for a number of purposes connected with our business operations, which include:

  * processing your orders or applications;
  * carrying out credit checking (unless we have agreed otherwise);
  * providing you with products and/or services requested;
  * billing you or administering your account;
  * dealing with requests, enquiries or feedback and other customer care related activities;
  * carrying out market and product analysis and marketing our products and services generally;
  * contacting you about our Geekdom’s product, services and promotions;
  * carrying out any activity in connection with a legal, governmental or regulatory requirement on us or in connection with legal proceedings, crime or fraud prevention, detection or prosecution.

We may also use your personal information for purposes related to those described above which would be reasonably expected by you. For example, we may use your personal information to keep you informed about features of our internet marketing education services or conducting analysis in order to provide better service to you. To opt-out of receiving certain Geekdom marketing materials, please send an email to [unsubscribe@geekversity.com.au](mailto:unsubscribe@geekversity.com.au) . Please note that Geekdom will still need to send you essential information about your account or changes to your service.

We will not use your information for purposes other than described above unless we have your consent or there are specified law enforcement reasons.

### How may Geekdom share your personal information?

Geekdom may disclose or receive personal information or documents about you to/from:

  * credit providers or credit reporting agencies for the purposes permitted under the Privacy Act;
  * law enforcement agencies to assist in the prevention of criminal activities;
  * our service and content providers, dealers and agents, or any company within the [Photon Group](http://www.photongroup.com/) for purposes that are related to providing you with an internet marketing education service which would be reasonably expected.

Unless you consent, we will not disclose your personal information to third parties, other than those who have contracted with Geekdom to keep the information confidential, or who are subject to obligations to protect your personal information.

### Security of your personal information

We will take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we collect, use or disclose is accurate, complete, up-to-date and stored in a secure environment protected from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.

How can you access your personal information?

Upon your request, Geekdom will take reasonable steps to let you know, generally, what sort of personal information we hold, for what purposes and how we collect, use and disclose that information.

Upon your request, Geekdom will provide access to your personal information we hold, except in certain prescribed circumstances, including emergency situations, specified business imperatives and law enforcement or other public interests.

### How to contact us

If you have any queries or concerns, please contact Customer Care by emailing [support@geekversity.com.au](mailto:support@geekversity.com.au) .

## Website Privacy Policy

Geekdom Pty Limited (Geekdom, we, us) is committed to respecting the privacy of your personal information. This website privacy policy explains our policy for dealing with personal information that we collect through our websites, geekversity.com.au, geekversity.com (our websites).

Throughout this policy, we refer to your ‘personal information’ which means information which identifies you as an individual or from which your identity can be reasonably ascertained. Your address is an example of personal information. We will post any changes to this website privacy policy on our websites, so we encourage you to check this website privacy policy from time to time.

In addition to the provisions of this website privacy policy, there may also be specific and additional privacy provisions that apply to certain sections of our websites. Because those specific and additional provisions also relate to your privacy protection, we recommend that you review them wherever they appear. In the event of any inconsistency between the provisions of this website privacy policy and those other specific and additional provisions, the specific and additional provisions will prevail.

### Information collected

The information about you which we may collect through our websites includes any messages or comments you submit to us via an online form or the ‘Contact Us’ page i.e. through an email.

Our websites automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested.

### Cookies

We may set and access cookies on your computer. “Cookies” are small identifiers sent from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive, similar to a license plate, that help us to recognize you if you visit our websites again. Also our websites use cookies to track how you found our websites. Cookies are not designed to be used to get data from your hard drive, your email or any other personal information about you. To protect your privacy we do not use cookies to store or transmit any personal information about you on the Internet. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings. Please note, however, that if you reject our cookies, it is possible that some web pages may not properly load, your access to certain information may be denied or you may have to enter information about you more than once.

### Use and disclosure of information

We may share personal information with other service providers including organisations that assist us by providing archival, auditing, consulting, mailhouse, delivery, technology and security services.

In addition to providing our services to you, we may use or disclose personal information that we collect about you:

  * for the purposes for which it was collected
  * where you have consented to the use or disclosure
  * to maintain our relationship with you
  * where a third party acquires or wishes to acquire, or makes inquiries in relation to acquiring, an interest in us, or
  * to the extent that we are required or authorised by law to do so.

We may also use your personal information to keep you informed of our services, developments and other matters. If you do not wish to be contacted for those purposes, please let us know using the contact details set out below. We aim to provide you with information and invitations that we consider may be of interest or relevance to your business.

### Links

Our websites may, from time to time, contain links to the websites of other organisations which may be of interest to you. Linked websites are responsible for their own privacy practices and you should check those websites for their respective privacy statements.

### Security

We use a number of mechanisms to protect the security and integrity of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed as completely secure. So while we strive to protect such information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once any personal information comes into our possession, we will take reasonable steps to protect that.

### Access to information

If you wish to request access to any personal information which we hold about you as a result of our information collection practices outlined in this website privacy policy, please contact us using the ‘Contact Us’ set out below. Please provide as much detail as you can about the particular information you seek, in order to help us retrieve it. An access fee may be charged to cover our costs of providing the information to you.

### Contact details

If you have any questions or feedback about privacy, or wish to make a complaint about the way in which we have handled your personal information, you may email [support@geekversity.com.au](mailto:support@geekversity.com.au) .
